mobiloud.com 2019-06-26

# MobiLoud - Privacy Policy

Through the MobiLoud service, we, Fifty Pixels Ltd (trading as "MobiLoud"), provide website operators and other individuals with a number of tools, services and assistance (including this website) to enable them to create, publish, and manage mobile applications.

This Privacy Policy applies to information that we collect about you when you use:

Throughout this Privacy Policy we’ll refer to our website, mobile applications and other products and services collectively as “Services.”

Below we explain how we collect, use, and share information about you, along with the choices that you have with respect to that information.

We only collect information about you if we have a reason to do so–for example, to provide our Services, to communicate with you, or to make our Services better.

We collect information in three ways: if and when you provide information to us, automatically through operating our services, and from outside sources. Let’s go over the information that we collect.

It’s probably no surprise that we collect information that you provide to us. The amount and type of information depends on the context and how we use the information. Here are some examples:

We do not sell our users’ private personal information.

We share information about you in the limited circumstances spelled out below and with appropriate safeguards on your privacy:

While no online service is 100% secure, we work very hard to protect information about you against unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction, and take reasonable measures to do so.

MobiLoud is a worldwide service. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing, transfer, and storage of information in and to the U.S. and other countries, which may have rights and protections that are different from those in your home country.

Ads appearing on any of our Services may be delivered by advertising networks. Other parties may also provide analytics services via our Services. These ad networks and analytics providers may set tracking technologies (like cookies) to collect information about your use of our Services and across other websites and online services. These technologies allow these third parties to recognize your device to compile information about you or others who use your device. This information allows us and other companies to, among other things, analyze and track usage, determine the popularity of certain content, and deliver advertisements that may be more targeted to your interests. Please note this Privacy Policy only covers the collection of information by MobiLoud and does not cover the collection of information by any third party advertisers or analytics providers.

If you’d like to use third party services like plugins, SDKs, crash logging, advertising and analytics tools with our Services, please keep in mind that when you interact with them you may provide information about yourself to those third parties. We don’t own or control these third parties and they have their own rules about collection, use and sharing of information. You should review their rules and policies when installing and using third party software.

If you are a user to one of our Users’ apps please note that this privacy policy doesn’t apply to you in regard to that specific app. We process limited information that users provide to our Users’ apps on behalf of our Users and in accordance with our Terms and Conditions. We encourage our Users to post a privacy policy that accurately describes their practices on data collection, use, and sharing of personal information.

The section above of our Privacy Policy is available under a Creative Commons Sharealike License and is based on Automattic's Policy.

MobiLoud collects some Personal Data from its Users.

## Owner and Data Controller

Fifty Pixels Ltd, 209 High Road, N2 8AN London

**Owner contact email:** support@mobiloud.com

## Types of Data collected

Among the types of Personal Data that MobiLoud collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: first name; last name; phone number; email address; VAT Number; company name; address; country; state; province; ZIP/Postal code; various types of Data; city; User ID; website; Cookies; Usage Data; unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example); geographic position. 

Complete details on each type of Personal Data collected are provided in the dedicated sections of this privacy policy or by specific explanation texts displayed prior to the Data collection.  
Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or, in case of Usage Data, collected automatically when using MobiLoud.  
Unless specified otherwise, all Data requested by MobiLoud is mandatory and failure to provide this Data may make it impossible for MobiLoud to provide its services. In cases where MobiLoud specifically states that some Data is not mandatory, Users are free not to communicate this Data without consequences to the availability or the functioning of the Service.  
Users who are uncertain about which Personal Data is mandatory are welcome to contact the Owner.  
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by MobiLoud or by the owners of third-party services used by MobiLoud serves the purpose of providing the Service required by the User, in addition to any other purposes described in the present document and in the Cookie Policy, if available.

Users are responsible for any third-party Personal Data obtained, published or shared through MobiLoud and confirm that they have the third party's consent to provide the Data to the Owner.

## Mode and place of processing the Data

### Methods of processing

The Owner takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.  
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Owner, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of MobiLoud (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third-party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Owner at any time.

### Legal basis of processing

The Owner may process Personal Data relating to Users if one of the following applies:

  * Users have given their consent for one or more specific purposes. Note: Under some legislations the Owner may be allowed to process Personal Data until the User objects to such processing (“opt-out”), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases. This, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Data is subject to European data protection law;
  * provision of Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with the User and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof;
  * processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Owner is subject;
  * processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the Owner;
  * processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner or by a third party.

In any case, the Owner will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract. 

### Place

The Data is processed at the Owner's operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located.

Depending on the User's location, data transfers may involve transferring the User's Data to a country other than their own. To find out more about the place of processing of such transferred Data, Users can check the section containing details about the processing of Personal Data.

Users are also entitled to learn about the legal basis of Data transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by the Owner to safeguard their Data.

If any such transfer takes place, Users can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this document or inquire with the Owner using the information provided in the contact section.

### Retention time

Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for.

Therefore:

  * Personal Data collected for purposes related to the performance of a contract between the Owner and the User shall be retained until such contract has been fully performed.
  * Personal Data collected for the purposes of the Owner’s legitimate interests shall be retained as long as needed to fulfill such purposes. Users may find specific information regarding the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner within the relevant sections of this document or by contacting the Owner.

The Owner may be allowed to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever the User has given consent to such processing, as long as such consent is not withdrawn. Furthermore, the Owner may be obliged to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever required to do so for the performance of a legal obligation or upon order of an authority.

Once the retention period expires, Personal Data shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after expiration of the retention period.

## The purposes of processing

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its Services, as well as for the following purposes: Contacting the User, Analytics, Tag Management, Displaying content from external platforms, Hosting and backend infrastructure, Remarketing and behavioral targeting, Handling payments, User database management, Traffic optimization and distribution, Content commenting, Infrastructure monitoring, Commercial affiliation and Interaction with external social networks and platforms. 

Users can find further detailed information about such purposes of processing and about the specific Personal Data used for each purpose in the respective sections of this document.

## Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

### Analytics

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

#### Google Analytics (Google Inc.)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of MobiLoud, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). 

#### MixPanel (MixPanel)

MixPanel is an analytics service provided by Mixpanel Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://mixpanel.com/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://mixpanel.com/optout/). 

#### Wordpress Stats (Automattic Inc.)

Wordpress Stats is an analytics service provided by Automattic Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/). 

#### Facebook Ads conversion tracking (Facebook pixel) (Facebook, Inc.)

Facebook Ads conversion tracking (Facebook pixel) is an analytics service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects data from the Facebook advertising network with actions performed on MobiLoud. The Facebook pixel tracks conversions that can be attributed to ads on Facebook, Instagram and Audience Network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant. 

#### Google Analytics for Firebase (Google Inc.)

Google Analytics for Firebase or Firebase Analytics is an analytics service provided by Google Inc.  
**In order to understand Google's use of Data, consult[Google's partner policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)**.

Firebase Analytics may share Data with other tools provided by Firebase, such as Crash Reporting, Authentication, Remote Config or Notifications. The User may check this privacy policy to find a detailed explanation about the other tools used by the Owner.

MobiLoud uses identifiers for mobile devices and technologies similar to cookies to run the Firebase Analytics service.

Users may opt-out of certain Firebase features through applicable device settings, such as the device advertising settings for mobile phones or by following the instructions in other Firebase related sections of this privacy policy, if available.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example); Usage Data. 

Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant. 

#### Hotjar Form Analysis & Conversion Funnels (Hotjar Ltd.)

Hotjar is an analytics service provided by Hotjar Ltd.  
Hotjar honors generic Do Not Track headers. This means your browser can tell its script not to collect any of your data. This is a setting that is available in all major browsers. Find Hotjar’s [opt-out information here](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: Malta – [Privacy Policy](https://www.hotjar.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out). 

#### Google Ads conversion tracking (Google Inc.)

Google Ads conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Google Inc. that connects data from the Google Ads advertising network with actions performed on MobiLoud.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant. 

#### Facebook Analytics for Apps (Facebook, Inc.)

Facebook Analytics for Apps is an analytics service provided by Facebook, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/). 

#### Woopra (Woopra)

Woopra is an analytics service provided by Woopra Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.woopra.com/privacy/). 

### Commercial affiliation

This type of service allows MobiLoud to display advertisements for third-party products or services. Ads can be displayed either as advertising links or as banners using various kinds of graphics.  
Clicks on the icon or banner posted on the Application are tracked by the third-party services listed below, and are shared with MobiLoud.  
For details of which data are collected, please refer to the privacy policy of each service.

#### Lead Dyno (LeadDyno, LLC)

Lead Dyno is a commercial affiliation service provided by LeadDyno, LLC.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; email address; first name; last name; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.leaddyno.com/terms-of-service/). 

### Contacting the User

#### Contact form (MobiLoud)

By filling in the contact form with their Data, the User authorizes MobiLoud to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header.

Personal Data collected: address; city; company name; country; email address; first name; last name; phone number; province; state; User ID; various types of Data; VAT Number; website; ZIP/Postal code. 

#### Mailing List or Newsletter (MobiLoud)

By registering on the mailing list or for the newsletter, the User’s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning MobiLoud. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to MobiLoud or after making a purchase.

Personal Data collected: email address; first name; last name; phone number. 

#### Phone contact (MobiLoud)

Users that provided their phone number might be contacted for commercial or promotional purposes related to MobiLoud, as well as for fulfilling support requests.

Personal Data collected: phone number. 

### Content commenting

Content commenting services allow Users to make and publish their comments on the contents of MobiLoud.  
Depending on the settings chosen by the Owner, Users may also leave anonymous comments. If there is an email address among the Personal Data provided by the User, it may be used to send notifications of comments on the same content. Users are responsible for the content of their own comments.  
If a content commenting service provided by third parties is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the comment service is installed, even when Users do not use the content commenting service.

#### Disqus (Disqus)

Disqus is a content commenting service provided by Big Heads Labs Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy) – [Opt out](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/1657951). 

#### Facebook Comments (Facebook, Inc.)

Facebook Comments is a content commenting service provided by Facebook, Inc. enabling the User to leave comments and share them on the Facebook platform.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation). 

#### Comment system managed directly (MobiLoud)

MobiLoud has its own internal content comment system.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; email address; first name; last name; website. 

### Displaying content from external platforms

This type of services allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of MobiLoud and interact with them.  
This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

#### YouTube video widget (Google Inc.)

YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows MobiLoud to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.it/intl/en/policies/privacy/). 

#### Gravatar (Automattic Inc.)

Gravatar is an image visualization service provided by Automattic Inc. that allows MobiLoud to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.  
Please note that if Gravatar images are used for comment forms, the commenter's email address or parts of it may be sent to Gravatar - even if the commenter has not signed up for that service.

Personal Data collected: email address; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/). 

#### Vimeo video (Vimeo, LLC)

Vimeo is a video content visualization service provided by Vimeo, LLC that allows MobiLoud to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://vimeo.com/privacy). 

### Handling payments

Payment processing services enable MobiLoud to process payments by credit card, bank transfer or other means. To ensure greater security, MobiLoud shares only the information necessary to execute the transaction with the financial intermediaries handling the transaction.  
Some of these services may also enable the sending of timed messages to the User, such as emails containing invoices or notifications concerning the payment.

#### PayPal (PayPal Inc.)

PayPal is a payment service provided by PayPal Inc., which allows Users to make online payments using their PayPal credentials.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

#### Stripe (Stripe Inc)

Stripe is a payment service provided by Stripe Inc.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/terms/US). 

### Hosting and backend infrastructure

This type of services has the purpose of hosting data and files that enable MobiLoud to run and be distributed as well as to provide a ready-made infrastructure to run specific features or parts of MobiLoud. Some of these services work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the actual location where the Personal Data are stored.

#### Amazon Web Services (AWS) (Amazon)

Amazon Web Services (AWS) is a hosting and backend service provided by Amazon.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

Place of processing: See the Amazon privacy policy – [Privacy Policy](https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant. 

#### Google Cloud Storage (Google Inc.)

Google Cloud Storage is a hosting service provided by Google Inc.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/). 

### Infrastructure monitoring

This type of service allows MobiLoud to monitor the use and behavior of its components so its performance, operation, maintenance and troubleshooting can be improved.  
Which Personal Data are processed depends on the characteristics and mode of implementation of these services, whose function is to filter the activities of MobiLoud.

#### Firebase Performance Monitoring (Google Inc.)

Firebase Performance Monitoring is a monitoring service provided by Google Inc.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant. 

#### Crashlytics (Google Inc.)

Crashlytics is a monitoring service provided by Google Inc.

Personal Data collected: geographic position; unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example); various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://try.crashlytics.com/terms/privacy-policy.pdf). 

### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

This type of service allows interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of MobiLoud.  
The interaction and information obtained through MobiLoud are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network.  
This type of service might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.  
It is recommended to log out from the respective services in order to make sure that the processed data on MobiLoud isn’t being connected back to the User’s profile.

#### Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook, Inc.)

The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation). 

### Remarketing and behavioral targeting

This type of service allows MobiLoud and its partners to inform, optimize and serve advertising based on past use of MobiLoud by the User.  
This activity is performed by tracking Usage Data and by using Cookies, information that is transferred to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity.  
In addition to any opt out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

#### Perfect Audience (NowSpots, Inc.)

Perfect Audience is an advertising service provided by NowSpots, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.perfectaudience.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://www.perfectaudience.com/privacy/index.html#opt-out). 

#### Google Ads Remarketing (Google Inc.)

Google Ads Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Google Inc. that connects the activity of MobiLoud with the Google Ads advertising network and the DoubleClick Cookie.

Users can opt out of Google's use of cookies for ads personalization by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated).

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout). Privacy Shield participant. 

#### Facebook Remarketing (Facebook, Inc.)

Facebook Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects the activity of MobiLoud with the Facebook advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/). 

#### Facebook Custom Audience (Facebook, Inc.)

Facebook Custom Audience is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects the activity of MobiLoud with the Facebook advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; email address. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/). 

#### Remarketing with Google Analytics (Google Inc.)

Remarketing with Google Analytics is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Google Inc. that connects the tracking activity performed by Google Analytics and its Cookies with the Google Ads advertising network and the Doubleclick Cookie.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout). Privacy Shield participant. 

### Tag Management

This type of service helps the Owner to manage the tags or scripts needed on MobiLoud in a centralized fashion.  
This results in the Users' Data flowing through these services, potentially resulting in the retention of this Data.

#### Segment (Segment Inc.)

Segment is a tag management service provided by Segment.io, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://segment.com/docs/legal/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant. 

#### Google Tag Manager (Google LLC)

Google Tag Manager is a tag management service provided by Google LLC.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). 

### Traffic optimization and distribution

This type of service allows MobiLoud to distribute their content using servers located across different countries and to optimize their performance.  
Which Personal Data are processed depends on the characteristics and the way these services are implemented. Their function is to filter communications between MobiLoud and the User's browser.  
Considering the widespread distribution of this system, it is difficult to determine the locations to which the contents that may contain Personal Information User are transferred.

#### Cloudflare (Cloudflare)

Cloudflare is a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by Cloudflare Inc.  
The way Cloudflare is integrated means that it filters all the traffic through MobiLoud, i.e., communication between MobiLoud and the User's browser, while also allowing analytical data from MobiLoud to be collected.

Personal Data collected: Cookies; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/). 

### User database management

This type of service allows the Owner to build user profiles by starting from an email address, a personal name, or other information that the User provides to MobiLoud, as well as to track User activities through analytics features. This Personal Data may also be matched with publicly available information about the User (such as social networks' profiles) and used to build private profiles that the Owner can display and use for improving MobiLoud.  
Some of these services may also enable the sending of timed messages to the User, such as emails based on specific actions performed on MobiLoud.

#### Intercom (Intercom Inc.)

Intercom is a User database management service provided by Intercom Inc. Intercom can also be used as a medium for communications, either through email, or through messages within our product(s).

Personal Data collected: email address; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://docs.intercom.io/pricing-and-terms/privacy). 

#### HubSpot CRM (HubSpot, Inc.)

HubSpot CRM is a User database management service provided by HubSpot, Inc.

Personal Data collected: email address; phone number; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.hubspot.com/legal/privacy-policy). 

#### HubSpot Lead Management (HubSpot, Inc.)

HubSpot Lead Management is a User database management service provided by HubSpot, Inc.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.hubspot.com/legal/privacy-policy). 

## Further information about Personal Data

### First Promoter

First Promoter is a commercial affiliation service provided by Igil Webs SRL. 

Personal Data collected: Cookies, email address, first name, last name and Usage Data.

Place of processing: Romania – [Privacy Policy](https://firstpromoter.com/privacy)

### ProfitWell

ProfitWell is a payment service provided by OK, LLC.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.profitwell.com/privacy-policy)

### Xero

Xero is an accounting and invoicing service provided by Xero Limited.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: New Zeland – [Privacy Policy](https://www.xero.com/uk/about/terms/privacy/)

## The rights of Users

Users may exercise certain rights regarding their Data processed by the Owner.

In particular, Users have the right to do the following:

  * **Withdraw their consent at any time.** Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.
  * **Object to processing of their Data.** Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent. Further details are provided in the dedicated section below.
  * **Access their Data.** Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing.
  * **Verify and seek rectification.** Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected.
  * **Restrict the processing of their Data.** Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it. 
  * **Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed.** Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.
  * **Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller.** Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that the Data is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on the User's consent, on a contract which the User is part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.
  * **Lodge a complaint.** Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.

### Details about the right to object to processing

Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection.

Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document. 

### How to exercise these rights

Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month.

## Cookie Policy

MobiLoud uses Cookies. To learn more and for a detailed cookie notice, the User may consult the [Cookie Policy](https://www.iubenda.com/private/privacy-policy/23762/cookie-policy "Cookie Policy").

## Additional information about Data collection and processing

### Legal action

The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of MobiLoud or the related Services.  
The User declares to be aware that the Owner may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities. 

### Additional information about User's Personal Data

In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, MobiLoud may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular Services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request. 

### System logs and maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, MobiLoud and any third-party services may collect files that record interaction with MobiLoud (System logs) use other Personal Data (such as the IP Address) for this purpose. 

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Owner at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document. 

### How “Do Not Track” requests are handled

MobiLoud does not support “Do Not Track” requests.  
To determine whether any of the third-party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies. 

### Changes to this privacy policy

The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page and possibly within MobiLoud and/or - as far as technically and legally feasible - sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. 

Should the changes affect processing activities performed on the basis of the User’s consent, the Owner shall collect new consent from the User, where required. 

###  Definitions and legal references 

#### Personal Data (or Data)

Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.

#### Usage Data

Information collected automatically through MobiLoud (or third-party services employed in MobiLoud), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use MobiLoud, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment.

#### User

The individual using MobiLoud who, unless otherwise specified, coincides with the Data Subject.

#### Data Subject

The natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.

#### Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)

The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Controller, as described in this privacy policy.

#### Data Controller (or Owner)

The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of MobiLoud. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of MobiLoud.

####  MobiLoud (or this Application) 

The means by which the Personal Data of the User is collected and processed.

#### Service

The service provided by MobiLoud as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this site/application.

#### European Union (or EU) 

Unless otherwise specified, all references made within this document to the European Union include all current member states to the European Union and the European Economic Area. 

#### Cookies

Small piece of data stored in the User's device.

#### Legal information

This privacy statement has been prepared based on provisions of multiple legislations, including Art. 13/14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation).

This privacy policy relates solely to MobiLoud, if not stated otherwise within this document.

Latest update: May 29, 2018
